# **AKSHATHA K**

### **Summary**

Determined and knowledgeable software developer who can think outside the box. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP,OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

## **Skill Highlights**

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver

- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

### **Experience**

**Software Developer Wordpress** – May 2022 to July 2023 **Biztechnosys**, Bangalore

**Web Developer Intern** – September 2018 to November 2018 **Code Trappers**, Bangalore

**Computer Science Lecturer** – January 2011 to June 2013 **VCET**, Puttur

#### **Education**

Master of Technology: **Computer Science**- 2013 to 2015

Canara Engineering College, Mangalore

Percentage: 72%

Batchelor of Technology: Computer Science- 2006 to 2010

Moodlakatte Institute of Technology, Kundapura

Percentage: 65%

#### **Technical Skills**

# **Projects**

CRM doctor store

https://store.crm-doctor.com

CRM DOCTOR

https://crm-doctor.com/crmdoctor

**CMS PARADISE** 

https://cmsparadise.com/

**BIZINFRATECH** 

https://bizinfratech.in

My Portfolio - using HTML/CSS

https://akshathakbhat.github.io/